export const generalQuestions=[{
        question: ' Are the Comments, DMs, Or Follows/Unfollows Automated?',
        answer:
            "  We use automation in our services; however, we are using it sparingly. We prefer to employ less intrusive methods that will contribute to the organic growth of your account. A prime example is the likes and Story views, both tested methods that enhance the visibility of your profile without risking getting your account suspended.\n",
        index:0
    },
    {
        question: "Do you Offer Any Deals or Discounts for Registering Multiple Accounts?",
        answer: "At the moment, we have some special offers for multiple accounts. If you purchase our services for two accounts, you can benefit from a 10% discount. For four accounts, there is a 25% discount, and for ten or more accounts, you can benefit from a 40% discount"
        ,index:1
    },
    {
        question: 'Is There any Risk of Being Suspended or Blocked from Instagram for Using Your Services? ',
        answer: "We guarantee you that your account will never be suspended or blocked due to our services. We offer real Instagram likes from active users on the platform. For this reason, your account isn’t at any risk of being suspended or blocked."
        ,index:2
    },
    {
        question: "Do the Likes You Are Offering Come from Real Users?",
        answer: "Yes, we make sure to provide likes by real users that are active on the platform."
        ,index:3
    },
    {
        question: "Do You Offer Any Other Services Along with Views, Likes, and Followers?",
        answer: "Right now, our services include only likes, views, and followers. However, there are future plans to expand our services in the following months. Please, visit our website to keep up-to-date with our services."
        ,index:4
    },
    {
        question: "Can I Divide the Likes your Provide Amongst Several of My Posts?",
        answer: "Of course, you can divide the likes among several posts. However, this is only possible for content that was published after you have registered for our services. With this feature, we offer you the ability to divide the likes into up to 15 posts. With this method, you make sure that all of your posts get the love they deserve, even when you don’t have the time to personally boost them. With a total number of 15 posts, you make sure that not one of them will be left behind."

        ,index:5},
    {
        question: "Is it Possible to Work on Instagram?",
        answer: "It is possible to work and profit on Instagram. Below, you will find some useful tips that will help you get started. We will cover the topics of marketing on Instagram and how you can become an influencer."
        ,index:6
    },
    {
        question: "What is the Best Way to Collaborate with Celebrities and Influencers?",
        answer: "The first step for a successful collaboration with celebrities and influencers on Instagram is that you need to find the ones that express your values and personality. If you do that, an influencer will provide you with much-needed social proof, which is the best way to promote your product or service. However, if you fail in collaborating with an influencer that is close to your brand image, their audience will just dismiss your product or service.\n"+
            "In case you are an influencer, you should also think similarly. There is no pressure for you to partner with brands that don’t represent your values. Your audience follows you because you are authentic and you stand for the things you promote. If you are disingenuous, then your image will suffer and you will lose a significant number of followers."
        ,index:7
    },
    {
        question: "How to Establish an Unforgettable Brand?",
        answer: "Establishing an unforgettable brand is a sure way to get Instagram followers. When users find a brand they like, they will return for more. Below, you will find tips to build your brand, gain more followers, and increase your ROI. \n" +
            "•\tPost Frequently and Be Consistent \n"+
            "When you are building an Instagram account, you should always keep a schedule and be consistent. Don’t overthink what you are going to post. Make sure that you regularly publish new content and that you keep your posts consistent.\n" +
            "•\tBoost your Posts with Hashtags" +
            "Hashtags begin with the # symbol and they are used to find similar posts on Instagram and other social media. With these tools, you can help other users find and follow your account. With the right use of a hashtag, you can also become a part of your niche’s community and create one of your own.\n" +
            "•\tHost Giveaways" +
            "There is no denying that users love to enter giveaways. For this reason, social media are full of brands that host contests for various products. The only thing that you need to do is to ask your users to like, share, and follow the post of your giveaway. This simple strategy will dramatically increase the number of your followers with the minimum cost.\n"
        ,index:8
},{
        question: "Is There a Way to Make my Posts Go Viral?",
        answer: "Social media platforms have millions of users and so, every successful post has the chance to go viral. However, you can’t know beforehand which post is going to get shared. Users are unpredictable and sometimes your quick posts become more successful than the ones you took the extra effort to create. Even though we can’t be sure of what makes a post go viral, there are certain trends that consistently bring a lot of shares.\n"+
            "Some posts that get always shared on social media are the following:" +
            "•\tMotivational and funny quotes" +
            "•\tMemes" +
            "•\tTutorials and DIY projects" +
            "•\tUnique and original photos" +
            "•\tFunny videos and fail compilations" +
            "•\tBehind the scenes footage" +
            "•\tUser-generated content" +
            "•\tSocial Media Challenges" +
            "One thing that you need to do no matter your posts is to always brand your images. This way, even if your post gets shared, all users will know that it’s your creation.\n"+<b/>+
            "Growing the Number of your Followers\n" +
            "Nevertheless, there is one thing that will definitely make your brand strong on Instagram and that is a huge number of followers. Nowadays, you can do that in multiple ways, by getting followers organically, by buying Instagram followers or buying Instagram likes. Buying your following should be the first thing on your list when establishing your brand. If you take extra care to create content that your audience is going to like and appreciate, then the number of your followers will constantly increase.\n"
        ,index:9
    },
    {
        question: "Will Working with An Agency Bring Me Better Results?",
        answer: "   Instagram doesn’t have any limits as to who can post on the platform. This means that everyone has the potential of becoming an influencer if he finds a way to attract users’ attention. For example, a teenager can gain a lot of attention by posting consistent content that users like, while a big company struggles to gain any traffic.\n" +
            "For this reason, companies that want to build a presence on Instagram, usually work with an agency that will help them grow their account. The agency has professionals that know how to make any account stand out from the competition and start gaining the audience’s attention.\n" +
            "•\tCan I buy Instagram followers as a Company?" +
            "As a company on Instagram, you face a lot of competition. In your case, an agency will give you the right solutions for your industry. The agency will create a plan for the development of and organic content that will boost your account. This way, you will learn how to gain followers and how to create content that gets likes. In addition to this, you can buy real followers and Instagram likes from Likes.io, the best agency that provides you with followers and likes. By doing this, you enhance your brand and create opportunities for more future sales. \n" +
            "•\tCan I get Even more Followers as an Influencer?" +
            "If you are an aspiring influencer, then you are probably thinking of new ways to get more Instagram followers. In this case, working with an agency is the best idea. They will guide you to buy real Instagram followers that will boost your account and your brand’s reputation.  More followers mean a greater engagement rate, and this also means an increase in your prices.\n"
        ,index:10
    },
    {
        question: "What is the Reason Why I Am Losing Followers?",
        answer: "The Instagram algorithm periodically goes through the accounts of its users. They examine the accounts that other users marked as spam and sweep them. If some of your followers are accounts like this, you might notice a sudden drop in followers.  If you notice that this thing happened within 30 days after you have purchased our services, we will make sure to replenish your followers."
        ,index:11
    },
    {
        question: "Is There a Way to Cancel the Followers That I Purchased from Tagiamtop",
        answer: "All of the followers we provide you are real Instagram users. This means that we can’t transfer or remove them. If there are some individual accounts you wish to remove from your follower list, you can block them one by one."
        ,index:12
    },
    {
        question: "What Can I Do if I Don’t Want Follower Replenishment?",
        answer: "If you wish to stop follower replenishment, you should let us know by sending an email at support@likes.io."
        ,index:13
    },
    {
        question: "How Often Do You Conduct Follower Replenishment?",
        answer: "We make sure to conduct follower replenishment every 24 hours. Once we detect a follower drop, our system begins the process."
        ,index:14
    },
    {
        question: "Is there a Limit to the Followers I can Buy?",
        answer: "There is no limit as to how many times you can purchase our services. However, the cumulative number of followers should not surpass 100,000 followers within 30 days."
        ,index:15
    },
    {
        question: "Do I Need to Provide Your with Passwords And Credentials To Purchase Your Services?",
        answer: "The only thing that we require of your is your account’s username. You don’t have to provide us with your passwords or your other credentials."
        ,index:16
    },
    {
        question: "How Can You Provide Real Likes from Real Accounts?",
        answer: "We have worked hard to build a large network to provide you with superior services. Our numerous contacts among Instagram users allows us to get you all the real likes and followers you need."
        ,index:17
    },
    {
        question: "What Are the Payment Methods you are Accepting?",
        answer: "At the moment, you can settle your bills with Cryptocurrencies, Apple Pay, and all cards. Nevertheless, we are planning on introducing more payment methods in the future to add more convenience to you."
        ,index:18
    },
]

export const billingQuestions=[
    {
        question: "What Are the Payment Methods you are Accepting?",
        answer: "At the moment, you can settle your bills with Cryptocurrencies, Apple Pay, and all cards. Nevertheless, we are planning on introducing more payment methods in the future to add more convenience to you."
        ,index:0
    },


]

export const frequentQuestions=[
    {
        question: 'Does Instagram know when I buy likes?',
        answer:  "No, Instagram has no method of knowing the difference between natural likes and those you purchase. To the platform, all of these likes are legitimate and permanent. As such, there is no risk in using our services.",
        index: 1
    },
    {
        question: "How to buy likes on Instagram for another account?",
        answer: "The best likes are accounts that will like your content and find it useful or interesting. One of the best ways to grow your account is by engaging with likes of accounts similar to yours, whether they are your competition, industry influencers or in closely linked fields.\n" +
            "All you have to do is give us a few accounts that have likes you think will like your content, then we target those specific demographics. Select the location and demographic of your desired likes and the hashtags they search for regularly, and we will do everything else to make sure you get your likes and engagement from the right place.\n" +
            "Of course, you can manually find new potential likes by searching for a location or hashtag and then seeing which accounts are suitable and relevant. This method is simple but slow, making it difficult to achieve long-term growth."
        ,index:2
    },
    {
        question: 'Do you need my password?',
        answer: "Our priority is real organic growth, with real followers and valuable engagement. Long-term results are more important to us than quick wins. You can monitor the progress of your campaign to see how it’s going, but we can’t guarantee how long it will take to reach your target. When you buy Instagram likes the cheap and easy way with Likes.io, we can help you keep growth on track with the strategic increase I likes and Story views that keep your account authentic.\n" +
            "We care about providing high-quality social media growth, and with great posts from you, you can see results after just a few days.",
        index:3
    },
    {
        question: "How much will it cost you?" ,
        answer: "We’ve created the safest and most stable growth platform possible, but automation does have some risks. Any type of third-party use on Instagram can risk blocks and bans, but it’s not common at all. We’ve never had an account get banned.\n" +
            "We avoid using overly intrusive or spamming methods, and instead look to engage real accounts, and encourage them to engage with your posts. We are also experts at staying on top of every Instagram update and requirement, so we can minimize risk as much as possible."
            ,index:4
        },
    {
        question: "What is the delivery time?" ,
        answer: "On every social media platform, people like following accounts that are popular. Just as how people like eating at restaurants with lots of customers, they want to be part of something tested - this idea is known as ‘social proof’.\n" +
            "Buying likes on Instagram is a great way to boost the ‘social proof’ of your posts, as the more likes you send, the more likely you are to get return engagement. By using Likes.io to buy likes for other posts, you can increase the visibility of your account and grow your followers organically.\n" +
            "Manually finding and scrolling through hundreds of relevant accounts will take up a lot of your time. Instead of concentrating on your core business objectives, you’ll be flicking through Instagram trying to find good accounts to like and engage with. Likes.io removes this time burden and provides a much easier way to use Instagram.\n" +
            "Our services can grow your popularity and enhance your reputation, giving you and your brand the platform you need to meet business goals. Buying Instagram likes with Likes.io leads to a stronger audience and a more engaged community."
        ,index:5
    },
    {
        question: "Are bought Instagram likes real?" ,
        answer: "Yes, it’s fast and easy. Just give us your account name, explain your growth goals, and we’ll do the rest.\n" +
            "Once we have the demographics, locations, interests and hashtags of the people you’d like to follow your account, we can do the rest. Just monitor your growth campaign on our platform and see how quickly your social presence can develop.\n" +
            "If you want to share your brand with the world, paid Instagram engagement is a great way to get started, as it is timely and strategic. You’ll see your followers and your engagement steadily begin to rise, which starts to attract the interest of other users."
        ,index:6
    },
    {
        question: "Can I lose the likes I bought?",
        answer: "Yes, it’s fast and easy. Just give us your account name, explain your growth goals, and we’ll do the rest.\n" +
            "Once we have the demographics, locations, interests and hashtags of the people you’d like to follow your account, we can do the rest. Just monitor your growth campaign on our platform and see how quickly your social presence can develop.\n" +
            "If you want to share your brand with the world, paid Instagram engagement is a great way to get started, as it is timely and strategic. You’ll see your followers and your engagement steadily begin to rise, which starts to attract the interest of other users."
        ,index:7
    }

]
